{"id":"2017_18","name":"Romans Lesson 182017_18","memoryVerse":"“If you declare with your mouth, ‘Jesus is Lord,’ and believe in your heart that God raised him from the dead, you will be saved.” – Romans 10:9","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2017_18_1","questionText":"1. What was meaningful to you in the lecture?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_18_2","questionText":"2. What help did you receive from the notes?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Romans 10:14-15.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:14-15"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_18_3","questionText":"3. How does Paul describe the steps to believing in Jesus Christ in verses 14-15?  Share your personal progression through the steps to believing in Jesus.","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_18_4","questionText":"4. Summarize the “good news” from your study of Romans.","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_18_5","questionText":"5. What is your role in sharing the good news with family, friends and the world?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Romans 10:14-15.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:14-15"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_18_6","questionText":"6. Give at least one point about the proclamation of the gospel from each reference.   Matthew 28:18-20","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Matthew","verse":"28:18-20"}]},{"id":"2017_18_6b","questionText":"6.   Acts 1:8","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Acts","verse":"1:8"}]},{"id":"2017_18_6c","questionText":"6.   Acts 13:46-47","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Acts","verse":"13:46-47"}]},{"id":"2017_18_6d","questionText":"6.   Romans 15:20","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"15:20"}]},{"id":"2017_18_6e","questionText":"6.   2 Corinthians 2:12-14","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"2 Corinthians","verse":"2:12-14"}]},{"id":"2017_18_6f","questionText":"6.   2 Corinthians 10:15-16","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"2 Corinthians","verse":"10:15-16"}]},{"id":"2017_18_7","questionText":"7. To whom does Paul’s quotation from Isaiah 52:7 refer? Why were their feet beautiful?","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Isaiah","verse":"52:7"}]},{"id":"2017_18_8","questionText":"  8. How is God calling you to take His message of grace into places filled with despair?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Romans 10:16-17.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:16-17"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_18_9","questionText":"  9. From a human perspective, why do people not respond positively to the good news when they hear it?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_18_10","questionText":"10. According to verse 17, from where does faith come? What does this teach about the importance of studying the Bible?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_18_11","questionText":"11. Share a time the Bible brought forth or strengthened your faith?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Romans 10:18-21.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:18-21"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_18_12","questionText":"12. Try to describe Paul’s logic in verses 18-21. How would you explain the differences in hearing, understanding and believing?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_18_13","questionText":"13. To whom were Moses and Isaiah referring in verses 19-20? ","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_18_14","questionText":"14. Where has God strategically placed you to share the Bible’s truths? How might you encourage someone today?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Read Romans 10:14-21.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:14-21"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_18_15","questionText":"15. What have you learned about God in this week’s study? How may your group pray for you as you make this truth a part of your life?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_18_16","questionText":"16. Homiletics for discussion and administrative leaders: Romans 10:14–21","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:14"}]}]}}}